It's a different world. He fits in perfectly.
Mr. Monk's Last Case: A Monk Movie is a comedy, crime,
mystery film directed by Randall Zisk.
Monk steps out of retirement as his stepdaughter's wedding turns
tragic when her fiancé dies in a bungee jumping accident.
Adrian Monk, played by Tony Shalhoub.
Natalie Teeger-Albright, played by Traylor Howard.
Randall 'Randy' Disher, played by Jason Gray-Stanford.
Trudy Monk, played by Melora Hardin.
Dr. Neven Bell, played by Héctor Elizondo.
Leland Stottlemeyer, played by Ted Levine.
Monk's Last Case: A Monk Movie is a 2023 American
comedy mystery film directed by Randy Zisk.
It is a sequel to the USA Network television series Monk, and
was written by series creator Andy Breckman.
Tony Shalhoub, Traylor Howard, Jason Gray-Stanford, and Ted Levine reprised their roles as the main
characters from the show, while recurring actors Melora Hardin and Héctor Elizondo also appeared.
Set twelve years after the series finale, the film follows Adrian Monk, a private detective with obsessive–compulsive disorder and
multiple phobias, who comes out of retirement and reunites with his friends to solve a case involving his stepdaughter.
The film premiered on Peacock on December 8, 2023.
The film explores themes of san francisco, california, obsessive compulsive
disorder (ocd), private detective, nostalgic, mental disorders.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.